Redmond, please!
You share the same blood!
Don't do this!
Severin, just say you're sorry!
Forget the wedding!
We’ll run away from Emeraldstone tonight and never come back!
I can't lose you!
Mother, don’t be afraid.
No noble on all of Golantis would dare touch me.
Keep bragging.
You clearly don’t know  who the Blade Master is.
When he's done with you,
you'll wish you were never born.
Redmond, let it go.
No need to
waste time on him.
The counts and lords are waiting to witness our wedding.
Fine.
If this loser and his dirt-buddies get on their knees,
slap their own faces,
and beg me for mercy...
I might let them crawl out alive.
You heard him, Severin.
Get on your knees.
Even the High King of Golantis cannot make me kneel.
What makes you think this pathetic little insect can?
I tried to save you, Severin!
If you want to commit suicide, fine!
But don't drag your mother and these
innocent idiots down with you.
Forget him, Livia!
Trash like this only learns respect when he sees blood.
Severin, if you insist on digging your own grave,
then so be it.
Severin, please!
Just listen to her!
Apologize to Redmond!
He spit on my people,
and you think I should bend?
Today, I am erasing House Carter.
It’s time for you snobs to feel what absolute power looks like.